<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BDI Code Club</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BDI Code Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Version control with Git and RStudio</title>
      <link>/post/version-control-git-rstudio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/version-control-git-rstudio/</guid>
      <description>Some BackgroundWhy Git?What is Git?The general Git workflowWhat’s the difference Git and GitHub?Getting Started with Git, GitHub, and RStudioInstalling GitCreating a GitHub accountStarting a new project with GitBeginning from RStudioBeginning from GitHubOtherHelpful ResourceR-centered linksHappy Git and GitHub for the useR from Jenny Bryan and Jim Hester is a great place to continue from here, with a focus on R, RStudio, and GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing the maximum computation power of your computer on R</title>
      <link>/post/utilizing-the-maximum-computation-power-of-your-computer-on-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/utilizing-the-maximum-computation-power-of-your-computer-on-r/</guid>
      <description>NotePlease open your R-Studio as an administrator.
OverviewIn this tutorial, we introduce a package to use multiple cores of your system.
After this tutorial you will be able to:
Train a neural network model without using multicoresTrain a neural network model without using multicoresCompare resultsUsing R MarkdownThe tutorial that follows was created using R Markdown. As an exercise in using R Markdown, here, we ask you to save your work in an R Markdown file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDI Code Clinic</title>
      <link>/page/about-full/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about-full/</guid>
      <description>The Big Data Institute (BDI) is an interdisciplinary research institute that focuses on the analysis of large, complex, heterogeneous data sets for research into the causes and consequences, prevention and treatment of disease.Our coding club’s ambition is to create a fun and supportive environment where we develop programming and statistics skills together, across programming languages.We have a many experts in working with Python, R, C++ and many more languages with vast knowledge of cloud computing and HPC and we want to replace statistics anxiety and code fear with inspiration and motivation to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDI Code Club</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Some info here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>